welcome to the class on neural dynamics
欢迎来到神经动力学课程
neural dynamics is part of the larger
神经动力学属于计算机神经科学
field of computational neuroscience
领域的一部分
computational neuroscience works on a
计算神经科学的工作原理基于
theoretical description of the brain
我们的大脑的理论研究
our brain is organized in different areas
大脑组织在不同的领域
there is an area involved in visual
其中有一个区域进行视觉的
information processing called the visual cortex
信息处理，这就被叫做视觉皮质
imagine that you are riding a bicycle
皮质层想象你正骑着自行车
and in a certain distance you
然后看见距离你一定距离的
see a light switching from red to green
灯光从红色变为绿色
the information about the change of light color
这些相关的颜色变化
will enter through your eye
会透过你的眼睛进入
and go to visual cortex
然后到达你的视觉皮层。
now you have to decide whether you want to speed up
现在你必须决定是否需要进行加速
or whether you say well it's not worth
或者你觉得这不需要加速。这不值得这样做
doing it I'm not going to make it and
我可以不需要进行加速
you continue just as normal
你继续像往常一样
while you make your decision different areas of
当你做决定时，大脑的不同区域
the brain are involved
都参与进来了
finally you decide I want to speed up your motor
最后你决定我需要去加速
cortex sends out a command and your legs move faster
大脑皮质发出命令然后你的腿比之前移动的更快了。
the description on the level
关于不同脑误差水平
of different brain errors is a rather
的描述是本课程的一个
cause description
非常重要的描述
in this class we will take a different approach
在本课程中，我们将采用不同的方法
we will focus on one small cubic millimeter say of brain area
我们将集中讨论大脑的一小块区域
and this like little area of a cubic millimeter
就像这个块区域一样 约一立方毫米，
you'll find 10,000 cells
你会发现10,000个细胞
or so and these cells form an integrated network
和这些细胞形成一个网络
the cells involved in information
这些在大脑中
processing in the brain are
涉及到信息处理的细胞
called the neurons
称为神经元
neurons have different parts
神经元拥有不同的部分
there's a part called the dendrite
这一部分被称为树突(dendrite),
this is where information from other neurons will arrive
其他神经元的信息从这里到达
the soma is where the new one decides whether
这个胞体(soma)会做出新的决定
it's going to send out a signal or not
它会发出信号或者不发出
and then this signal travels along the
然后这个信号沿着
axon to other neurons
轴突到其他神经元
each neuron makes contacts to thousands of other neurons
每个神经元与数以千计的其他神经元接触
the contact points are called the synapses
这些接触点称为突触(synapses)
so the axon will branch out
所以轴突(axon)将信号分散出来
and make different ramifications
产生出不同的结果
and therefore we have not just the cells with a cell body
因此这我们不仅有细胞体的细胞
but we have a lot of wire
而且我们有很多相连的线
in fact in each small area of or
事实上，在每个小区域或
small volume of one millimeter cube
1毫米立方体的体积小，
you will have about 10,000 neurons and
你可以找到大约10,000个神经元和
several kilometers of wires
几公里的电线
what you see here on the left hand side is a drawing of harmonica
你看到左边的线状图
how we did this kind of
我们如何在100年前
drawing over 100 years ago
就可以画出这副图
and this gives a glimpse of the integral Network that those neurons form
这让我们看到了这些神经元形成的完整网络
however only a glimpse
虽然只是粗略的
and it's still a simplification
它仍然是一个简化
because wherever you see empty space here
因为无论你在哪里看到空的地方
in fact there would be other cells
实际上这里会有其他细胞
there would be other neurons
会有其他的神经元存在
there would be more material in the end
最终会有更多的物质
the brain consists of a fairly densely packed material
大脑由一个相当密集物质的组成
neurons synapses wires is everywhere
神经元突触无处不在
now I mentioned already that
到处都是我已经提到过的
these neurons send out signals
这些神经元发出信号
the signal consists of a short electrical pulse
信号由短的电学脉冲组成
called an action potential or spike
被称为动作电位或脉冲
an action  potential has a duration of a few milliseconds
动作电位有几毫秒的持续时间
and it has an
它的幅度约为
amplitude of about 100 millivolt
100毫伏
it's netic electrical signal
这是NETIC电信号
it's an electrical pulse one may ask the question
电脉冲可能会问这种问题
how this kind of pulse
这种脉冲是怎么回事
how thiskind of electrical signal is generated
这些电学信号是怎么产生的
just as any other cell
就像任何其他细胞
neurons are surrounded by a cell membrane
神经元被细胞膜所包围
in the cell membrane you will find pores
在细胞膜上，你会发现这些毛孔
these pores can open and close
这些毛孔可以打开和关闭，
and while the pores are open ions can flow in an area of the cell
毛孔是开放的通道，离子可以在一个区域内流动
these ions carry an electrical
这些离子携带电子
charge and contribute to the
改变和有助于
generation of this electrical pulse of
产生动做电位的
the action potential
电脉冲
next week we will develop models
下周我们将讨论这种模型
we will talk about models of this biophysical
谈谈这种生物物理学的模型
interaction of ions molecules
离子分子与这些的相互作用
and these models are called hodgkin-huxley type models
这种模型被称为hodgkin-huxley类模型
or biophysical models preferring
或说是生物物理模型
hodgkin-huxley who got a Nobel Prize
hodgkin-huxley得到了诺贝尔奖
for developing the first mathematical
因为发现了第一个关于神经元信号
description on the level of molecules of
在分子水平的
the neuronal signals
数学模型
now these models are rather complicated
现在 这个模型相当复杂
they discard the biophysics
他们放弃了生物物理学
in the week after week two we will try to reduce the complexity of the description
在第二周，我们将减少这个模型的复杂度
and we'll talk about
我们将谈论
simplified model types
简化的模型类型
now particularly simple model is a model where we say
简单模型是我们所说的模型
well we don't really care about the
好，我们真的不关心
biophysical mechanisms
生物物理机制
that contribute to the formation of an action potential
导致动作电位的形成
we just describe the action potential as
我们只是将动作电位描述为
a pulse a standard pulse
一个脉冲标准脉冲
so suppose a pulse arrives from a presynaptic neuron from a sending neuron
所以假设脉冲来自发送神经元的突触前神经元
it arrives
这个脉冲到达
it goes over the synapse
越过了突触
and it causes a response on the postsynaptic side
它会引起突触后的反应
on the side of the receiving neuron
在接受神经元的这一侧
the postsynaptic neuron is the neuron receiving the signal
突触后神经元是接收穿过
that goes across
突触的接触点的信号
the contact point across the synapse
的神经元
so this input pulse here will cause
此输入脉冲将导致
this response over there
此处的响应
now this new one will receive not just one input
现在这里不仅会收到一个新的输入
but it will receive input pulses from many
而且将接收来自许多不同神经元
different neurons
的输入脉冲，
suppose many different pulses arrive
假设许多不同脉冲到达
then the effects of all these different pulses will be added up
这些影响和全部不同的脉冲将被叠加起来
so this describes how different incoming
所以这描述了不同的输入
pulses are transformed into a response of the receiving cell t
脉冲转化为接收单元的响应
his response is
它的回应
called the postsynaptic potential
被称为突触后电位
but this does not yet tell us what makes
但是这还没告诉我们是什么导致这些
this cell here decide but they will send
这个细胞在这里决定， 但他们会
out a signal itself or not
发送出信号本身或者会不发送信号
now the formation of a pulse
现在在这个模型中
is triggered in this model
触发了一个脉冲
if this membrane potential
这种膜电位
if this postsynaptic potential reaches a value theta a threshold value
如果突触后电位达到阈值Theta，
at this point a spike is
此时的阈值是尖峰
triggered and exponentially sent out
触发并发送了信号
and afterwards we have some reset of the
之后膜电位进入的到了
membrane potential to a low value
一个比较低的值静息电位
so this kind of model which are called
因此这种模型被称为
indicating fire model
IF模型
in this kind of models spikes are formal events
在这种模型中，峰值是正式时间
they are triggered at the moment
峰值产生当
when the membrane potential crosses the threshold
膜电位超过阈值时
and then a spike is sent out
然后发出一个尖峰
and after the spike there's some reset
然后尖峰会下降和上升
and refract on us a simple version of this model
这个模型的简单版本
will be the topic for today
将是今天的主题
and it will come back to this model
回到这个模型
towards the end of this series of lectures
在这一系列课程结束时
suppose now we have this kind of model
现在假设我们有这种模型
and our noon receives many many spikes from other
从其他神经元收到很多脉冲
neurons to make things simple
做一下假设来进行简化
we assume that spike arrival is random
我们假设这个脉冲是随机的
as a result of this the potential will fluctuate as
因此，电位将作为时间的函数而改变
a function of time and only
仅仅与时间相关
occasionally a spike is send out
只是偶尔发出一个尖峰，
so spikes are rather rare events trigger that a threshold
所以尖峰是一个触发到阈值产生的事件
below the threshold in the regime which
下面在政权阈值，其
is called sub threshold regime
这被称为阈值机制
what we observe and the random spike arrival is
我们观察脉冲随机到达
a fluctuating membrane potential and
一个波动的膜电位和
this is reminiscent of what one finds if
这让人想起如果发现了什么
neural activity is recorded with an
神经活动记录与
electrode in an egg Mouse for example
例如 ，鸡蛋中的电极
you see these fluctuations of the
你看到的这些波动
membrane potential and spikes are rare
膜电位和尖峰非常稀少
events from time to time a spike is sent out
事件不时发送尖峰
so in lectures in week five and six
因此在第五周和第六周的讲座
the last questions what do these
解决这个问题
fluctuations means is this noise what's
波动意味着这是什么噪音
the meaning of these action potentials
这些动作电位的意义
what's the information transmitted by
什么是传输的信息
the neuron what is the neural code
神经元是什么神经代码
so overall I will present this week a
总的来说， 我将在本周提出一个
first simplified model of a neuron
第一个简化的神经元模型
then in the next week we will go on to
在接下来的一周，我们将继续
hodgkin-huxley models
讲解hodgkin-huxley模型
simplify and reduce to what's called a feature Nagumo model
然后 我们将其简化并缩减为所谓的nagumo模型
we will talk about the dendrite
我们将谈论树突
we will talk about neural coding
我们将谈论神经元编码
we'll talk about the question of noise
我们将谈论的噪声的问题
about the question of what is the
还有关于
information processed and transmitted by an urn
信息是怎么处理和传输的问题
and in week seven in a final lecture
在最后的第七周课程
I will put these different
讲座我会把这些不同
things together and show how to extract
事情集中在一起，并展示如何提取
from neural data a model of a neuron
来自神经数据的神经元模型
which is able to describe neural
这能够描述神经
information processing to describe to
要描述的信息处理
transform implant incoming signal input into output spikes
变换植入输入信号输入输出
and therefore shed
因此脱落
light on the questions of coding and decoding
关于编码和解码的问题
after this short introduction
在这个简短的介绍后
I would now like you to do a first little exercise
现在想要你先做一点联系
please take two or three minutes
花费两到三分钟
and answer the following questions
并回答以下问题
and then I will continue with
然后我会继续讲解
a first model
第一个模型